Health room. The population of Gaza Strip is 2.2 million people.
49% of them are women.
And women in Gaza do not have access to hygiene water, to personal hygiene supplies, to ministerial supplies, to sanitary pads.
They don't have access to all these things.
And women now are simply exposed to psychological and physical health risks because there are no products to use during their periods.
Women are shy to tell you this, but they don't have to be shy actually.
The world is not shy to let us to death for 62 days now.
So they don't have to be shy to tell you that there are no pads to use in Gaza.
And that there is a new suffering on lockdown.
We're suffering from being hungry, from being thirsty, from being bombed.
We're suffering from being displaced.
Now we're suffering also because there is no pads.
It's just a new suffering.
The thing is, I don't know where is the UN women, where is the UNFPA, where is the UNICEF, the UNRWA, where is the rest of the INGOs.
I don't know if there are, they are not wise enough to put pads to, in the, in the aid trucks that enter Gaza rarely, taba'an.
This, um, this is too much.